NEW YORK
The future.
A dark desolate world.
World in war,
suffering, loss ..
.. on both sides.
Mutants and the humans who dared help them,
fighting an enemy we can not defeat.
Are we destined on this path?
Destined to destroy ourselves
like so many species before us?
or can we evolve fast
enough to change ourselves?
Change our fate?
Is the future truly set?
Sync & Completed By: Hasantha
http://www.baiscopelk.com
They are here!
Time's-up !
Sentinel!
Sunspot.
Let's go!
Blink!
No!
It's too late, assholes !
Come here!
Get your hands up!!
-Get down !!
-No!!!
No !!!
So few of us left.
Professor.
We found them.
-Bobby.
-Hi, Storm.
Hey, kid.
Professor.
You made it.
Whenever the Sentinels attack
Warpath spots them.
and I sent Bishop back to
warn us of the attack...
before it happens.
Blink scouts the next side and..
.. well then we leave before
they ever know we were there.
Because we never were.
What do you mean you've never  there?
She projects Bishop back in time few days...
to warn the others of the coming attack.
She sends Bishop back in time?
No, just his consciousness,
in to his younger-self
into his younger body.
Wow!
This not just work, Charles.
What might works?
The Sentinel program was originally conceived by Dr. Bolivar Trask.
In the early 70s he was one of the world leading weapons designers.
But, covertly he had began experimenting only mutants.
Using their gifts to fuel his own research.
There was one mutant who had
discovered what he was doing.
Mutant with ability to
transform herself to anyone.
Mystique.
I knew her as  Raven.
We met when we were
children, grow up together.
She was like a sister to me.
I tried to help her.
But only succeeded in driving her away.
She hunted Trask across the world.
And at the Paris Peace of Accords in 1973
after the Vietnam War.
She found Trask,
And killed him.
It was the first time she killed him.
Wasn't no last.
But killing Trask did not have
the outcome she expected.
It only persuaded the government
the need for his program.
They captured her that day.
Tortured her and experimented on her.
In her DNA, they discovered the secret
to her power of transformation,
it gave them the key they needed,
to create weapons that could
adapt to any mutant's power.
And less than 50 years,
the machines were destroyed so
many of our kind were created.
and It all started that day in 1973,
The day she first  killed,
The day she truly became Mystique.
Do you wanna go back there?
If I can get to her,
stop the assassination,
keep her out of their hands,
And we can stop the Sentinels
ever been borne.
And end this war,
before it  ever begins.
I can send someone back in couple of weeks.
Maybe a month, but you're talking about going back decades.
You have the most powerful brain the world, Professor.
But the mind can only stretch so far before it snaps.
It will rip you apart.
I'm sorry.
No one can survive that trip.
What if someone's mind has a
way of sniping back.
What if someone can heal as
faster as rip apart.
Okay, Spread out.
Take you position.
So I wake up in the my younger
body god knows where, then what?
You need to go to my house and find me,
convince me all of this.
Wouldn't you just be able to read my mind?
I didn't have my powers in 1973.
Logan, you have to do for me what I once did for you,
Lead me, guide me.
I was a very difference man then.
You have to be patient with me.
Patience  isn't my strongest suit.
You're  need me as well.
What?
After Mystique left Charles, she came with me,
and I set her on a dangerous path.
Darker path.
It's going to take the two of us side by side
at a time when we couldn't be further apart.
Great.
So where do I find you?
Oh..Its complicated.
Basically, your body goes to sleep,
only your mind travels back in time.
As long as you back there, past and present
will continue to coexist.
But once you wake up....
.. whatever you've done will take hold and become history.
And for the rest of us that will
be the only history that we know.
That will be like,
last 50 years never happened.
This world, this war.
The only person who'll
remember it,
...is you.
Alright Logan, I need you to clear your
head and stay as calm as possible.
What do you mean?
If your mind gets rocky, It will harder for me to hold you.
You could start to slip between past and future.
What I need to get a little rocky ?
Think  peaceful thoughts.
Peaceful thoughts.
Do you have any good news?
Well,
You don't really age so you'll
pretty much look the same.
You don't have much time in past.
Sentinels will find
us, they always do.
And this time we won't
be able to run or have no escape.
This is our last chance.
Do you really think this will work?
I have faith in him.
So do him right about his choice.
If he is young, It would
be no any better.
We'll know.
See you soon.
It might sting a little.
Holy Shit !!
It worked.
Hey, what's going on ?
-Gwen! Get dressed!
-Who are you?
Hey, I don't know what's going on.
What's going on is you supposed to guard
your Boss's daughter, not screwing her.
I didn't sleep with her.
-No?
-No.
I mean, yes
I slept with her many times, but...
Jimmy!
That wasn't me. That was old me.
-I just got here like 20 seconds ago.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-What happen to your cloths?
No...Oh..
Will you believe me if I told you
I've sent here from the future?
-Get out of here, Sweetheart.
-Yeah
We'll take care of this comedian.
No you not.
You gonna give me the keys of your car  and money for gas
or you gonna wake up in a hospital.
Trust me, I know how these things pay out.
-Because you from the future?
-No,
...because of these.
What the hell!!
Ahhh...Damn it.
Peaceful thoughts.
We are reviewing all of our defense expenditures
and all the black books are being opened.
We can't support a weapon that
targets our own citizens
If these mutants as you described,
Already living among us,
then they are living here peacefully.
- We haven't had an incident in over 10 years.
-After what happened in cuba?
It was never confirmed.
We have real enemies out there.
Russians, The Chinese.
We're talking about 10 of 10 of the 10
of our population.
-Allow me to read something to you.
-Please.
This was acquired by our
friends at the CIA.
Its in a dissertation,
written by a mutant
at Oxford University.
And I quote.
To Homo-neanderthals his a
mutant cousin of Homo Saphiens,
Which is us.
Was an aberration,
the arrival of mutated human
species: Homo Saphiens.
was followed by the immediate extinction
of the their less evolve kin.
Well,
Now..
We are the  Neanderthals.
Speak for  yourself,  Dr.. Trask.
You know when you send our soldiers to Vietnam without the weapon they needed to win the war
you underestimated your enemy.
You, hah you do that with this enemy,
It won't be some border skirmish
halfway around the world.
This time the war will be for our
streets, our cities, our homes.
And by the time you see
the need for my program,
it will be too late.
And you will have lost two
wars in one life time.
We're sorry, Dr.. Trask.
But your Sentinel Program,
It ain't gonna fly.
Can I help you, Colonel?
Just here to give my
boys to proper send off.
I'm sorry, sir. But we have orders.
This is a quarantined area.
Stand a side, soldier.
That's an order.
Attention.
At ease.
What is all this?
Lab reports, blood tests. All are
getting packed up and send back.
Where is it going?
Same place as they are.
Trask Industries.
Lets go gentleman
Taking you out of this shit show.
Shipping home?
Not just yet.
What do you doing with those?
Its only make the ride little smoother.
We are transferring you to a
private facility, where we can..
run a few more tests.
Your men are not military.
Private outfit.
We're authorized to command these men.
These troops are going home.
Well, colonel...
I don't believe you have the
jurisdiction in this matter.
I'm afraid I do it, son.
I'm sorry who are you?
The question is, Major.
Who are you?
Raven.
That's not my name.
-I had him.
-I know.
Let's move out.
Com-on let's go.
Where's Erik?
I'm on my own now.
Let's go. Move it.
Hold that plane!
I wanna leave these boys in this
godforsaken country
Let's go.
You're not coming with us, are you?
My war is not over.
The enemy is still out there.
Where did they go?
Four cadets where they go?
They went over there.
PRIVATE PROPERTY
KEEP OUT
XAVIER'S SCHOOL
Can I help you?
Ahh Yeah what happened to the School?
School has been shut for years.
Are you a parent?
Sure as hell hope not.
-Who are you?
-I'm Hank.
I and Maccoy,  look
after the house now.
You are Beast?
Look at you, guess you are a late bloomer.
I do not know what you're talking about.
I'm  gonna have to ask you to leave.
-Where is the professor?
-There is no professor here.
You're pretty strong for a scrawny kid.
Sure there is no Beast thing  here?
-Come on, Beast.
-Beast is not here.
-Come on, Beasty.
-Go!
Hey!!
I said, the school is closed.
You need to leave.
Not until I see the professor.
There is no professor here.
I told you that.
Look, kid.
You and I gonna be good friends.
You just don't know what yet.
Professor!
Ahhh.....
Hank, what's going on here?
-Professor.
-Please do not call me that.
Do you know this guy?
Yeah he looks slightly familiar
Get off the bloody chandelier, Hank.
You can walk.
You're a perceptive one.
I thought Erik ..
What you saying managed to
miss our sign on the way in
This is private property my friend, i'm
gonna ask him to ask you to leave.
Well, I'm afraid I can't do that because...
..because I was sent here for you
Well, tell whoever it was that sent you that I'm busy.
This gonna be a little tricky,
because the person who sent me..
was you.
-What?
-About 50 years from now.
50 years from now, like in the
future 50 years from now.
Yeah.
-I sent you from the future.
-Yeah.
Piss off.
If you had your powers,
you know I was telling the truth.
How do you know I don't have my.....
-Who are you?
-I told you.
-You are CIA?
-No.
You were watching me.
I know you, Charles.
We've been friends  for years.
I know your powers came when you were 9.
I know you thought, you were going crazy when
it started, all the voices in your head.
and it wasn't until you were 12 that you realized
all the voices were in everyone else's head.
Do you want me to go on?
I never told that anyone.
Not yet no but, you'll.
Alright you've picked my
interest, what do you want?
We have to stop Raven.
I need your help.
We need your help.
Think I'd like to wake up now.
What does she have to do with this?
So, you're saying that they
took raven's power and what?
They weaponized it?
Yep
She is unique.
Yes, she is.
In the beginning the sentinels
were just targeting mutants.
Then they began to identify
the genetics in non-mutants.
Who would eventually have mutant
children or grandchildren
Many of the humans tried to help us,
it was a slaughter
Leaving only the worst
of humanity in charge
But then it went worse.
I've never seen anything like this.
And it all starts with her.
Let's just say that for the sake of,
Sake that I choose to believe
you, that I choose to help you.
Raven won't listen to me.
No her heart and soul belongs
to someone else now.
I know.
That's why we gonna need Magneto, too.
Erik?
You do know where he is?
Yeah.
He's where he belongs.
So that's it, you're just gonna walk out?
Oh top marks, like I said,
you are perceptive.
The professor I know would
never turn his back
..on someone who lost their path
Especially someone he loved.
You know..
I think I do remember you now.
Yeah, we came to you a long
time ago seeking your help.
And I'm gonna say to you
what you said to us then,
Fuck off!
Listen to me you little
shit, I've come a long way,
and I watched a lot of people die,
good people, friends.
if you're gonna wallow in
self pity and do nothing,
Then you're gonna watch the
same thing, you understand?
We all have to die some time.
I told you, there is
no professor here.
What the hell happened to him?
He lost everything.
Erik, Raven, his legs.
The school allowed us this whole place
Just after the first semester,
The war
in Vietnam got worse.
Many of the teachers and
students were drafted.
It really broke him.
He retreated into himself..
I wanted to help do something so..
So I designed a serum to
treat his spine,
Derived from the same formula that
helps me control my mutation.
I take just enough to
keep myself balanced but,
he takes too much.
I tried easing him back but he
just couldn't bear the pain
Voices..
The treatment gives
him him his legs but
It's not enough
He's..
He's just lost too much.
You're not scare to me?
I always believed I couldn't be
the only one in the world.
Charles Xavier.
Raven .
You're hungry and alone?
Take whatever you want.
We got lots of food, you
don't have to steal. .
In-fact, you never have to steal again.
And that's a promise.
I hope you get her.
but not for any of your
future shots but for her .
Fare enough.
I'm telling you this, you do not know Erik.
The man is a monster.
A murderer.
You think you can convince Raven to change?
To come home?
Splendid.
But what makes you think
you can change the him?
Because you and Erik
sent me here back together.
The room they're holding him in was built during the
2nd world war when there was a shortage of steel
So the foundation is pure
concrete and sand, no metal.
And he's being held a 100
floors beneath the most,
Heavily guarded building on the planet.
Why is he in there?
What, he forgot to mention?
Ahhh JFK.
He  killed him?
What else would explain the bullet
miraculously curving through the air,
Eric's always had a way with guns.
Are you sure you want
to carry on with this?
This is your plan, not mine.
We don't have any resources to get us in,
or out
It's just me and Hank.
I know a guy.
Yeah, he'd be a young man now
grew up outside of DC
He could get into anywhere,
just don't know how the
hell we're gonna find him
History provided the question
We have a phone book
I thought you'd be getting
ready for your trip, sir.
I just came to grab couple of files.
Is that a new scarf?
It's nice.
Thank you.
AUTOPSY REPORTS
Dr. Trask.
One second.
We added some names to the Paris meeting
Thank you.
Is there something wrong, sir?
No.
It's nothing.
Would you mind typing up my itinerary.
I don't wanna miss anything.
What has he done now?
-I'll just write you a check for whatever he took.
-We just need talk to him.
Peter, the cops are here..
.. again.
Guess what, I didn't do anything
I've been here all day.
Just relax Peter, we are not  cops.
Of course you're not cops, if you were
cops you wouldn't drive a rental car
How'd you know we got a rental car?
I checked your registration when you
were walking through the door,
I also had some time to kill so I went through your
rental agreements, saw you were from out of town
Are you FBI?
No, you're not cops, hey what's
up with this kid's school place
That's an old card.
He is fascinating
He is a pain in the ass.
What teleporter?
No, He's just fast.
When I know him he was
so old. Young.
Young?
You're just old.
So you're not afraid to show your powers?
Power? What power? What
you talking about?
You see some strange here?
Nothing anybody believe if you told them.
So who are you?
What do you want?
We need your help, Peter.
What?
Break into a highly secured facility
and get someone out.
Prison break?
That's illegal, you know.
Well, only if you get caught.
What's there in for me?
You, the kleptomaniac, get
to break into the pentagon.
How do I know I can trust you?
Because we are just like you.
Show him.
It's cool, just disgusting
Built in 1943, the Pentagon is the
world largest office building.
Housing more than 25000 military and police
stretched over 6 million square feet.
Where  is the bathroom?
I need to pee.
Well, lucky for you, you have...
Thank you.
No Metal Beyond This Point.
Yeah, we getting broadcast signal down here?
What's going on?
Damn it !! Call the maintenance,
get them down here.
MIND THE GLASS
....from a Japanese empire.
This month long battle...
included some of the fearsome
fighting during world war II
In 3 seconds those doors are going to open,
and 20 guards will be here to shoot us.
I know, that's what i'm waiting for
What are you doing?
I'm holding your neck so
you won't get whip-lash
What?
Whip.....la..sh
They're in.
You're good. It'll pass.
It happens when I run.
Must have done something pretty serious.
What're you do, man?
What you do.
What're you do?
Why would they have you in there.
For killing the president.
Anything i'm guilty of is fighting
for people like us
You take Karate?
You're a Karate man?
I don't know Karate.
I know crazy.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls
this is a code red situation
We are evacuating the entire floor so that we,
my uh associate and I can uh
- Secure the prisoner.
- Who are you?
We are special operations
CB, FE, CIED look,
Perhaps you didn't hear
me what first I spoke
It's imperative that you understand
we're in complete lock down situation.
We have to get in to the 3rd floor
Oh, I'm sorry, you want to finish?
They told me you can control the metal.
They?
You know my mom once knew a
guy who could do that.
Sorry, I'm just not very
good with violence.
Charles.
Good to see you too, old friend.
-And walking?
-Not thanks to you.
You're the last person in the
world I expected to see today.
Believe me, I wouldn’t
be here if I didn't have to.
If we get you out of here we do it my way,
No killing.
No helmet.
I couldn't disobey you even if I want to.
I'm never getting inside
of that head again.
I need your word, Erik.
No body move!
Move it, right there!
Charles.
Don't move!
Hands up or we'll shoot!
-Freeze them, Charles.
-I can't.
Hands up!
No!
♪ If I could save time in bottle....
♪ The first thing I like to do...
♪ Is to save every day
'til eternity passes away...
♪ Just to spend them with you....
♪ If I could make days last forever...
♪ If words could make wishes come true..
♪ I'd save every day like a treasure and then..
♪ Again, I would spend them with you..
♪ But there never seems to be enough time..
♪ To do the things you want to do once you find them..
♪ I've looked around enough to know..
♪ That you're the one I want to go through time with..
Thanks kid.
Peter, thank you very very much.
You take care.
Yeah, safe flight man, *****,
why you want to go Paris?
Imagine if they made of metal.
Do me a favor and return it for me, okay.
Peter...
Take it slowly.
Where did they dig you up?
You're gonna find this
hard to believe, but ahh..
You sent me.
You and Charles,
from the future.
How did you lose them?
The treatment for my spine fixed my DNA.
You sacrificed your powers
that you could walk?
I sacrificed my power so that I could st..
What do you know about it?
I lost my fair share, hah.
Try your eyes, Erik.
It doesn't justify what you've done.
You've no idea what I have done.
I know that you took the
things that mean most to me.
Well, maybe you should have
fought harder for them.
Do you want to fight, Erik?
I'll give you a fight !!
-Let him come.
-You abandoned me!
You took her away and you abandoned me!
Angel.
Azazel.
Emma.
Banshee.
Mutant brothers and sisters all dead!
Congress on this
..experimented on, butchered
Erik.
Where were you, Charles?
We were supposed to protect them!
Where were you your own people needed you?
Hiding!
You and Hank, pretending you
were something you're not
Erik.
You abandon us all.
So you were always an asshole
I take it we're best buddies in the future
I spent a lot of years trying
to bring you down, bub
How is that work out for you?
You're like me.
You're a survivor.
You wanna pick all that shit up?
Paris
Excuse me.
I'm pretty sure it was my fault.
Wanna play a game? It's been a while.
I'm not in emotion for a game.
Haven't had a real sip in 10 years.
I didn't kill the president.
Bullet curved, Erik.
Because I was trying to save him.
They took me out before I could.
-Why would you trying to save him?
-Because he was one of us.
You must think me so foolish.
We always said they would come after us.
I never imagined they would
use Raven's DNA to do it.
When did you last see her?
The day I left to Dallas.
And how is she?
Strong.
Driven
-Loyal.
-How..
How was she?
She was..
I could see why she had so much talent.
You should be proud of her, Charles.
She is out there fighting for our cause.
Your cause.
The girl I knew, she was
not capable of killing.
You didn't raise her,
you grew up with her.
She couldn't stay a little girl forever
that's why she left
She left because you got inside her head
That's not my power.
She made a choice.
But now we know where that
choice leads, don't we?
She's going to murder trask,
they're going to capture her,
and then they're going to wipe us out.
Not if we get to her first.
Not if we change history tomorrow.
I'm sorry, Charles.
For what happened, I truly am
It's been a while since I played
I'll go easy on you.
Might finally get a fair fight.
You make the first move.
The diplomats from all around the
world arriving here today at the
hotel Royale.
It's a historic day as the official ending of,
the united states fierce
involvement in Vietnam.
There's the south Vietnamese foreign minister
with other south vietnamese dignitaries
The summit doesn't begin for another hour
The hotel has arranged a private room
upstairs for you, special quest
That'll be fine.
Good afternoon, everyone, hello.
Thank you for coming.
Congratulations on winning this war.
Now I know you all have hands to
shake and photos to take downstairs,
So I will get right to the point.
There is a new enemy out there.
An enemy that will render
your arsenals useless,
Your armies powerless and
your nations defenseless.
You'll need a new weapon for this war.
I call them "Sentinels".
Named after the ancient guardians
that stood at the gates of the citadel.
They have the aeronautic
capabilities of a Harrier Jet.
Armed with guns that can fire off,
more than 2000 rounds per minute with
thermo-ceramic ammunition.
But size, power, speed,
You can find that at Lockheed above.
No, what makes the
sentinels so special?
Is the ability to target
the mutant X gene?
The genetic guidance system that can
lock onto a mark half a mile away.
And won't trigger unless it
has identified the target.
With this weapon there'll be
no human collateral damage.
If I turn it on the system
couldn't even activate in here.
Unless...
...there's a mutant.
There has to be some kind of mistake.
My machine don't make mistakes.
What are you?
I assure you
I ..
No.Don't shoot him.
I assure you.
Do not arrest him.
I do not know what  you're talking about.
Raven!
Raven.
Charles.
We've come for you.
Erik and I.
Together.
I never thought I could
see you again.
I made you a promise long time
ago that I would protect you.
I didn't. And I know...
Wolverine!
I'm going to keep you safe
I'm going to keep you out of their hands
Erik.
What are you doing?
Securing our future.
Forgive me, Mystique.
Ss long as you're out there
we'll never be safe.
Erik.
Use your powers, Charles.
Stop him.
He can't.
He is slipping.
He is slipping back.
I'm loosing him.
Striker!
This is where you started
as Wolverine, okay?
Kitty!
Restrain him.
Erik!
Where am I?
Ahh.
How the hell did I get here?
What?
You came to us.
-Who are you?
-Charles.
Charles Xavier.
-I do not know you.
-Ahh?
What the hell is that?
Wow, ho I can deal with this.
Just go.
Stop, Erik.
Erik.
I'm sorry.
You are Logan.
That's Hank McCoy.
I'm Charles Xavier.
You spent the last couple of days with us.
You're on Acid?
Somebody gave you really bad acid.
Yeah?
Just hold on tight we'll
get through this together.
-Oh, God !
- Kitty.
She is wounded pretty bad.
I got him.
Professor.
What happened to you?
I just saw someone who's going to
bring me a lot of pain someday.
Where is Raven?
Gone.
-What?
-We have to get out of here.
Yesterday the paris peace summit was rocked
by the appearance of unidentified assailants.
The likes of which the
world has never seen.
Mass hysteria has gripped the
nation as people ask,
Where did they come from?
Will they'd be back?
And  most importantly,
Are they friend or foe?
That was one in corresponding to the earlier
reporting from the Paris Peace Summit yesterday.
What the hell are we dealing with here?
Off the record.
Two days ago,
This man Erick Lehnsherr escaped from a
maximum security prison inside the Pentagon.
We believe that this woman is a
former associate of lehnsherr's.
They were together in cuba
the day of the crisis in 1962.
Hs was also linked to the
Kennedy assassination.
What about that thing?
We do not know what that thing is, Sir.
Actually we really don't
know what any of them are.
Yes.
Yes, We do.
They are mutants.
He ​​has the power to control metal.
Last I checked that's what most
of your weapons were made of.
And she can transform into anyone.
A general.
A secret service man.
Even you, Mr. President.
She can walk into this office,
and order a nuclear strike,
if she was in the mood.
And that's only two of them.
Well, do we have any
countermeasures, any defense?
I was waiting for you to
ask me that question.
That's an experimental program, Sir.
Strictly off the books.
You're telling me these
mutants are out in the world,
And our best defense are
these giant metal robots?
Many of the mutants looks like us.
My sentinels can tell the difference.
I have 8 prototypes ready to go,
They're built out of a space
age polymer, not an ounce of metal on them.
I wanna make a demonstration,
I want the world
to know that we can protect them.
What do you need to get
these things operational?
I already gave that number to congress
Unfortunately they elected to shut me down.
It's going to cost a bit
more to turn them on.
Whatever you need.
Oh, and one more thing, if we
do manage to capture them,
I would like her for
research purposes of course.
Horrible.
What is it?
He was born like that.
True?
Just imagine ..
Reflecting and see the ugly face like that?
I can imagine.
Where did he come from?
Did he have a family?
Yes, she does.
If I see so much as a screw
I'll jam this into your throat.
How did you find me?
You taught me well.
It's been a long time
since we were this close.
I miss you.
You tried to kill me.
So the rest of us could live.
What do you mean?
I received a message from the future.
Don't lie to me.
I never have, I never will.
Humans use your blood, your genes to
create a weapon that wipes us all out.
I was only doing what I thought
necessary to secure our future.
So what's to stop me from killing you
right now and securing my future?
Nothing.
It doesn't matter anymore.
They have your DNA, your
blood was on the street.
Whose fault is that?
Mine.
I've seen their plans.
They are creating a weapon,
And now they have what they
need to take it further.
We have to strike now, while we have a
chance, while we still hold the upper hand.
I've seen too many friends die, Eric.
I don't want a war.
I only want the man who murdered them.
This is a war.
What happened to you?
Did you lose your way
when I was gone?
Are you still Charles’s' Raven?
Or are you Mystique?
Trask is the enemy.
Killing one man isn't enough.
It never was for you.
Good Bye, Erik.
What happened?
Can he walk?
He need his treatment.
Hank, I can hear them.
It's ok, I'll make it stop. I'll get it
Hey, Hey. Pull yourself together
It's not over yet.
You don’t believe that?
How do you know?
As these go,
This coming back.
They all come back.
Look, you know.
I'm still here.
She's still out there.
But we need your help, Charles.
Not like this,
I need you.
We can't  find Raven..
..not without your powers.
I added a little extra
cause you missed a dose.
Charles.
Hank, do me a favour.
Would you help me to my study please.
Gonna get you.
Are you sure about this?
Absolutely not.
This creature is extraordinary.
Her genes could hold the
key to mutation itself.
I need more.
That's all they were able to scrape off
the pavement in Paris.
More than blood.
I need brain tissue.
Spinal fluid.
Bone marrow.
Imagine sentinels that could
transform, adapt to any target.
If I just get my hands on her.
This girl could lead the program forward
years, decades into the future.
How old is your son now, Major?
Jason?
He's coming up on 10 now
if you can believe it.
Eight years from fighting age.
And how many of our sons and brothers did
we just ship home in body bags?
Maybe 50? 55000?
How many more in the other side?
Never before,
in all of human history,
Has there been a cause which
could unite us as a species?
Until now.
You really hate mutants doctor, don't you?
On the contrary, I rather admire
them the things they can do.
I assume mutants as our salvation.
And common enemy.
Common struggle against the ultimate enemy.
Extinction.
I believe our new friends are going
to help us usher in a new era, Bill.
A new era of genuine and
long lasting peace.
Attention! Attention!
Transport departure
in two hours.
Repeat.
Transport departure
begins in two hours.
When was the last time you down here?
-Last time we went looking for students.
- A life time ago.
Welcome, Professor.
Raven is wounded, she won't be moving fast.
These are muscles I haven't
stretched in a long time.
Gosh!
-No!
-Who are you?
Charles!
Charles, It's alright.
I'll go check the generator.
It's not the machinery, Is it?
-I can't do this, my mind...
-Yes you can.
-It won't take it.
-It's just a little rusty.
You do not understand, It’s
not a question of being rusty.
I can flip the switches,
I can turn the knobs.
But my power comes from
here, comes from ..
And it's broken.
I feel like one of my students.
Helpless.
It was a mistake coming down here.
It was a mistake freeing, Eric.
This whole thing has
been one bloody mistake.
I'm Sorry, Logan,
they sent back the wrong man.
You're right.
I’m.
Actually it was supposed to be you.
But I was the only one who could
physically make the trip.
And ahh don't know how long we've got here.
But I do know that a long time actually,
A long time from now.
I was your lost helpless student.
and you unlocked my mind.
You showed me what I was,
you showed me what I could be.
I don't know how to do that for you,
You're right, I don't.
But I know someone who might.
Look into my mind.
You saw what I did to Cerebro.
You don't want me inside your head.
There's no damage you can do.
That has already been done, trust me.
Hey.
-Hey, Logan.
-Hey, Jean.
-Kill me.
-I love you.
You're a..
..poor man.
Look past me.
I don't want suffering!
I don't want your future!
Pass my future.
Look for your future.
That's it.
Charles.
So this is what become of us?
Erik was right.
Humanity does this to us.
Not if we show them a better path.
You still believe?
just because someone
stumbles, loses their way,
It doesn't mean they're lost forever.
Sometimes we all need a little help.
I'm not the man I was.
I opened my mind,
It almost overwhelms me.
You're afraid.
and Cerebro knows it.
All those voices..
So..... much...... pain.
It's not their pain you're afraid of.
It's yours Charles.
And as frightening as it may be,
That pain will make you stronger.
If you allow yourself to feel it,
embrace it.
It will make you more powerful
than you ever imagined.
It's the greatest gift we have,
to bear their pain without breaking.
And it's born from the most human power
Hope.
Please,
Charles,
we need to hope again.
Find what you were looking for?
Power is back on.
Yes.
Yes it is.
She's lost too much blood.
-She can't keep going like this
-We have no choice, Bobby.
We can wake him up.
No.
They need more time.
I had a glimpse into the past,
If we wake logan now we may set off an
even darker course.
They need more time.
Raven, stop.
Stop running.
Charles.
Where are you?
Back at the house.
..where you should be.
I need you to come home.
I know what I need to do.
If you kill Trask,
You will be creating
countless more just like him.
Then I'll kill them too.
Those are Erick's works not yours.
The girl I grew up with
wasn't capable of killing,
She was good, fair, full of compassion.
I have compassion,
just not for Trask.
He's murdered too many of us.
Shut her down Charles, get in her head.
She's not letting me in I'm barely holding on.
I'm not strong enough yet.
I know what Trask has done.
But, killing him will not bring them back.
it will set you on a path from which
there is no return
An endless cycle of killing
us and them,
till there is nothing left.
But we can stop it  right now.
You and I.
You just have to come home.
I have to .
You haven't changed at all, Charles.
Like I said.
I know exactly what I have to do.
Where is he?
At an airport boarding a plane.
Plane to where?
Washington DC.
Hey guys,
There is something I need to show to you.
We're going backwards in time.
This the system I designed to
record any news about Paris,
over all 3 networks and PBS.
All three? wow
Yeah and PBS.
Look what I found.
Tomorrow in front of the white house the
president will make his announcement .
He'll be joined by secretary
of defense Blair.
And has even sought the help of
renowned scientist Bolivar Trask.
His special adviser to combat
this mutant issue.
White House is....
Raven doesn't realize but if she kills trask at
an event like that with the whole world watching
Then I came a long way for nothing.
And there's more bad
news, I saw in a report.
They found traces of her blood in paris.
for all we know they
already have her DNA .
That's all they need,
to create the
sentinels in the future.
Now there's a theory in time
physics that time is immutable.
It's like a river, you can throw a pebble and it will
create a ripple but the current always corrects itself.
No matter what you do the river just
keeps flowing in the same direction.
What are you trying to say?
I was saying is..
what if the war is inevitable.
What if she's meant to kill Trask.
What if this is just simply who she is.
Just because someone
stumbles, loses their way.
Doesn't mean they're lost forever.
I don't believe that  theory, Hank.
And I can not believe that who she is.
Ready the plane
we're going to washington.
Washington. D.C.
You alright ?
Getting there.
Whatever happens today, I need
you to promise me something.
You looked into my mind and you've seen
a lot of bad but,
You've seen the good too.
The X-Men.
Promise me you'll find us.
Use your power, bring us together.
Guide us. Lead us.
Storm,
Scott,
Jean.
Remember those names.
There's so many of us.
We will need you, Professor.
I will do my best.
Your best is enough.
Trust me.
12 carriers inbound, 10 miles.
They found us.
Thousands of people will be gathered here, they
come from all over the world witness history
Along with news crews from
at least 50 different countries.
Thank you.
Can I see your invitations please?
Yes you may..
these two are with me.
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
Logan.
Please, this way, sir.
It's fine...
I haven't found her yet
but she has to be here.
President of the United States.
My fellow Americans,
Today we face the greatest
threat in our history.
Mutants.
I'm pregnant..
We have prepared for this threat.
In the immortal words
of Robert Oppenheimer.
Behold..
The world will never be the same again.
Can I help you?
No, you can't.
Here they come.
This for you brothers and sisters.
Raven.
I have her.
Let me go, Charles.
There.
You see?
Secret service man
left to the stage.
-Got it.
-Go.
What the hell are you doing?
I didn't tell you to activate it.
I didn't.
Raven, please listen to me.
We've been given a second
chance to define who we are.
Don't do this.
********
Gentlemen, you cannot pass this point.
We can't stop that many.
No.
But, we can slow them down.
Erik!
Move it ! Comon let's go!!
Storm!
Take us to Def-con 3.
Mr. President we are code red.
Air defense ready now.
What the hell happened out there?
I'll fix it.
You said that before,
I wanted to make a statement.
Now the whole goddamn world knows
we can't protect them.
I will fix it.
You damn well better.
Charles!
Is everybody okay?
Storm!
Behind you.
Now.
I'm probably not supposed to
ask this kind of a thing.
But in the future,
do I make it?
No.
But we can change that, right?
Do what you were made for.
Mutants.
Where are you?
I got this. Go.
Oh dear god, no.
So much for being a survivor.
One of them is in here.
No! No! No!
Don't kill it.
I need it alive.
What the hell has happened?
You built  these weapons to destroy us.
Why?
Because you're afraid of our gifts.
Because we are different.
Humanity has always feared that
which is different.
But I'm here to tell you, tell the world.
You're right to fear us.
We are the future.
We are the ones who will
inherit this earth.
And anyone who stands in our way,
Will suffer the same fate as
these men you see before you.
Today was meant to be a
display of your power.
Instead I give you a glimpse of the
devastation my race can unleash upon yours.
Let this be a warning to the world.
And to my mutant brothers
and sisters out there,
I say this:
No more hiding.
No more suffering.
You've lived in a shadows in shame
and fear too long. Come out.
Join me, fight together in the
brotherhood of our kind.
New tomorrow.
..that starts today.
All those years wasted fighting
each other, Charles
To have a precious few of them back.
Mr. President.
Stand down ! I said stand down!
You want to make a statement?
Kill me...finally
But spare everyone else!
Very heroic, Mr. President.
But you had no intention
of sparing any of us.
The future of our
species begins now.
Mutant
Mutants
You used to be a better shot.
Trust me, I still I'm.
Get out of my head, Charles!
Raven,
Please do not make us the enemy
today.
Look around you, we already are.
They not all of us.
All you've done so far
Is save the lives
of these men.
You can show them a better path.
Shut her down, Charles
I've been trying to control you
ever since the day we met.
And look what that's got us
Everything that happens now,
is in your hand.
I have a faith in you, Raven.
He's all yours, Charles.
If you let them have me
I'm as good as dead.
You know that.
I know.
Good-bye, old friend.
Good-bye, Erik.
You sure you should let them go?
Yes.
I have hope for them.
It's going to be a time, Hank.
When we're all together.
What about Logan?
Good morning, Logan.
Late start. Hah hah ha.
Have a good lunch time.
Good job.
-Thank you.
-Very good job.
Storm.
Jean.
Hi, Logan.
Are you okay?
You're here.
Where else would I be?
Woh.
Easy, pal.
Some things never change.
Good to see you, Scott.
Ah ha.
See you later, Jean.
Professor.
Logan.
Is everything alright?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it is.
You did it.
Did what?
Logan, don't you have a class to teach?
A class?
To teach. What?
History.
History?
History, I could use some help with that.
Help with what?
Pretty much everything after 1973.
I think history I know
is little different.
Welcome back.
It's good to see you, Charles.
It's good to see everyone.
Well,
I had a promise to keep.
You and I have lot of catching up to do.
Yes.
What is the last thing you remember?
Drowning.
The past,
a new and uncertain world.
A world  of endless possibilities.
and infinite outcomes.
Can we?
Oh he is alive!
He is breathing
Countless choices define our fate.
Each choice, each moment a
ripple in the river of time.
What do you want us to do with him,
Major Striker?
Enough ripples and you
change the tide.
I'll take him from here.
For the future is never truly set.
Sync & Completed By: Hasantha
http://www.baiscopelk.com